thank you everybody thanks so much very
happy to be here
tonight wow did you guys hear that or
was that me man I'm I'm hearing voices
again anyway I'm very happy to be here
and I did a show here last night and
some lady asked if my hair was
natural I'm like where would you go to
get your hair done like this you
know she said petmart
and that stung a little bit but she was
right it's a really good deal
so I've been going back every four to
six
weeks and I'll tell you that flea bath
is tough man
but all right some of you are digging
this and some of you are looking at me
like didn't we see this guy under a
bridge earlier
[Music]
today that was me man I write these
jokes in the dirt and then come in and
try him out and I'm not looking forward
to this rain it's going to wipe out my
ACT thanks a lot I'm doing good on the
right side of the room
I'm as and Republicans over there but uh
no I am I'm a registered Republican
because I just like showing up to the
meetings and freaking them out you know
I'm like they're like you're not
supposed to be
here I'm like yeah I am when I tie my
hair back I look like that that guy on
the nickel
so you're like we got to let him in he's
on the
nickel all right now I'm so happy to be
doing shows again and and you know I fly
to most places I mean I'm not a good
driver I think you know when you get a
good look at me I don't think that comes
as a real shock I don't think you guys
are like I bet this guy can really drive
a car man I'm I'm not good behind the
wheel of an automobile if you look at me
I got a weird eye going that way uh
which makes it interesting it four-way
stops you
know they're like which way is this guy
going to go to
you that joke always does better over
here people over here like his eye is
the only normal looking thing on him
man all right but I am a bus rider and
weird things happen to me just in
general but you know the bus magnifies
it and this happened to me at a bus stop
in Colorado and I'm from Colorado but I
don't ski cuz I'm already sliding
downhill on so many other areas of my
life Wow thank you over there man I'm
GNA get the whole room to laugh and my
aisle straighten out just for a minute
there but this happened in Colorado it
was 8:00 at night it was this time of
year it was dark out and say like that
stool is the bus stop right I walk up to
the bus stop like you normally would and
I startled this woman who was there and
I get it I mean you know I'm a weird
looking guy however you want to say it
but we live in America here right we
have freedom of choice
like all right I'm doing well one person
at a time
man everybody's going to laugh it's just
individually but I have I've been there
before uh I'm not even a comic I came in
to get out of the cold for a while
said let me tell my
stories give me a bottle of water and
let me go up there no but what I'm
saying is we live in America you know we
have freedom of choice I choose to look
like this like
uh well people don't usually laugh there
but all right that's cool wherever you
guys laugh I'll slow down I get the
feeling there's something going on
behind me that I'm on aware of but but
no uh you know I I do I get up in the
morning check my reflection in the
mirror here I'm like that is the look
I'm going
for let's go to the bank I've got stuff
to do you know so so I walk up to this
bus stop I startle this woman and she
says to me are you all
right do you have somewhere to
go and I'm like yeah that's why I'm at a
bus
stop I'm going
places I don't think I can time it much
better is this your first time time at a
bus
stop and this happened to me um late at
night I'm riding a bus I'm a nightclub
Entertainer this guy stands up on a
rolling bus and asks me for a dollar and
first of all if you're asking me for
money I'm going to question your
analytical skills I
mean I do not look like a high
roller it's like do your homework but
uh this guy asked me for a dollar so I
try to be polite I'm like I'm sorry sir
I don't have a dollar and he cops an
attitude with me and starts talking all
tough he's like hey man why don't we
take our shoes off and do a little
boxing I know I'm like well that is a
weird request but I'm on this bus for
another 35 minutes so let's box
bro so as he was taking his shoes off I
beat the heck out of him you know like
you're the one who wanted to fight me
over a dollar
buddy and you know because I don't drive
I I walk a lot I that's my main form of
exercise and I try to get 10,000 steps a
day that's what the doctors tell you oh
thanks
yeah were you just clapping because
you're like I'll bet this guy didn't
even make 7,000 today but no I bought
one of those pedometers that you clip on
your belt you know and then I lost it so
I was bummed uh cuz I don't have a lot
of extra pedometer
cash laying around the house you know so
then I was like well I'll just keep
tracking my
head of my
steps and honestly that's what happened
to my eye man I was
like I was doing some heavy math
and my was like I'm not going to carry
the one anymore I'm out
oh thanks wow the old wandering ey Dr is
pan off thank you guys so then I sat
down on this sidewalk you know tried to
recount my
steps you guys are making up your own
jokes you know that I I'll set them up
you knock him down we'll be home time to
watch the weather but no I I sat down
you know and was retracing my steps I
went to the paint store for no apparent
reason you know thinking about some
other stuff someone walked by and they
thought I was inebriated you know so
they suggested 12
steps and I'm like I know I made it
farther than that
man that's like 40 feet tops if you're
taking big
steps all right you guys seem to be a
little bit of a math crowd and uh I've
got a math joke and it's a timely one if
I do say so myself because we're going
back to Standard time tomorrow and I
like daylight savings time better you
guys I do but you know how they say you
gain an hour when we set the clocks back
that's not really true but I came up
with a plan where you really do gain an
hour and it's called daylight driving
time and here's how it works you drive
95 miles an hour in a 65 mph zone for
[Music]
miles you have picked up an hour you
know that's the good news the bad news
is you're in Wyoming but you know
you're an hour ahead
so but I do go for a lot of walks and
I've walked around this town today uh
you know uh Provo and it's very nice
here uh but this happens to me wherever
I go you guys whether it's a city or
town you know whatever at least once
during the weekend a car will slow down
and yell at me you know uh not the cars
themselves but I
mean people in the cars right and what
they 99 times out of 100 is get a
job that was funny over there that's
good no but uh you know I I thought
about it it's like I have a job I
support uh comedy clubs restaurants
Airlines wherever I go so now when a car
slows down and you get a job I start
running alongside the car and I look
over and I'm like but I have a job and
it freaks out the driver you know
he's like it's not supposed to happen
like this supposed to yell at the weirdo
he's supposed to go back in the
alley how is he running 40 miles an
hour I'll tell you I can run 40 miles an
hour because I'm a bodybuilder and uh
yeah thanks you should see me when I'm
all oiled up I
uh so but I am I'm a I'm a bodybuilder
and I am selling a workout tape after
this um it's an audio
so I don't know if you have a cassette
deck but if you do you can have a body
like mine and
uh I'm not going to lie it's a cassette
Series so there's there's a lot of work
on there but there's some downtime on
some of those cassettes you know it's
just me going hey let's rest for a
while this is only tape one
tape two we're looking for a lighter the
whole tape
so that's
cardio man I really like where you guys
laugh sometimes you're there and other
times you're
like so but I'm selling those afterwards
and I'm having a special uh if you buy
an audio tape I will throw in a couple
of forever stamps with every purchase
all my money is tied up in forever
stamps uh I made some horrible
investments in
1989 and I have warehouses full of
forever
stamps across the United States so see
me afterwards
now um you guys seem to like the walking
jokes so I have some more walking jokes
um this one takes place in San Antonio
Texas San Antonio Texas very historical
you know like the alamo's right there
the club I'm working at one block on
this side of the Alamo the hotel I'm
staying at it's one block on the other
side of the Alamo so I'm always walking
back and forth in front of the Alamo you
know not like I'm on patrol like this
isn't going to happen again on my watch
you
know so uh there's a Ripley's Believe It
or Not right across from the Alamo and
the first day I'm in town I run into
Ripley and go I don't believe it
and that made him mad uh they threw me
out of Ripley and now I'm on a watch
list believe it or not and
uh I cannot go to any Ripley Believe It
or Not in North America you know and
honestly it really hasn't come into play
yet but uh but maybe one day so
anyway thank you another new person
welcome aboard uh but no I'm walking
this way and there's like a Rancher
looking guy walking towards me right and
I see him and I'm just like hey there's
a Rancher looking guy I wasn't like all
freaked out like oh no there's a Rancher
looking guy I was just like hey there's
a Rancher looking guy
yeah so I'm walking this way and as the
Rancher looking guy and I cross he says
to me hey
girl
so that voice in my head just says Hey
keep walking you know so I walk a few
more steps and then he says it again hey
girl so now I'm kind of flattered you
know so I turn around and he's flexing
and he says to me what do you have to
say for yourself and I'm like what kind
of women have you been
dating apparently you're into
Czechoslovakian po
Walters then he start Ed chasing me and
I outran him and I said hey a woman beat
you in a foot
race you guys are making me laugh man
that's
crazy a woman beat you in a foot race
how does that make you feel and he said
not very good and then I ran into Ripley
and said you're never going to believe
this all right I'm going to have a
little sip of water
here all right
like I say you guys seem to like the
walking jokes so here's another one this
one takes place in Virginia Beach
Virginia right and uh it's the same kind
of deal I'm there for like three or four
days doing shows I'm walking it's broad
daylight I'm crossing this road called
Independence Boulevard which is a big
road you know two lanes a median two
more Lanes not my first time crossing a
big road I mean I'm from Colorado but I
don't go hey my Shockers are
line I'm going to step off the curb here
and see what happens you
know so I'm walking and uh I have the
light and everything I get across the
two lanes I get across the median and
then I'm in the third lane and these
cars won't let me cross you know so now
it's like a weird game of
Frogger but I feel good CU I can look
both ways when I cross
I should do nothing but eye jokes that
should be the title of this special
nothing but eye jokes but I don't have
that many eye
jokes
so now it's getting serious and it
counts down to like five four three and
it gets to two and I throw my arms up in
disgust you know and then uh that car
stopped stops and I get across the
fourth lane and then uh that car makes a
ride and there's a Walmart trucker with
a big trailer and he makes the ride and
then as he's making the ride I see the
passenger side window going down and I'm
like he's going to yell at me and sure
enough he did and he said it said don't
walk you idiot so I started running
alongside the
truck and I looked over and it said but
it did say walk and he started throwing
Oreo cookies at me because he was mad
and then I started catching him and
eating him you
know and I said all you're doing is
carbo loading
me I'll run you all the way to the
coast all right that was
fun now I do uh you know I want to talk
about the environment a little bit it's
important to recycle you guys
and I recycle I do I'm a busy guy so I
do it all at once I melt down plastic
tin and aluminum all into one super
compound that I call
plastini and so far all I've made is a
knife out of it but I'll tell you this
nobody's giving me any trouble on the
bus anymore you know I'm like how about
some plastini pal
I found if you're ever getting a knife
fight I always throw that hand up there
like that cuz when they're looking up
there just a little knife fighting tip
for me to
you on a Saturday
night and you know there are things you
can do to help the environment like I
mentioned riding the bus Recycling and
I'm a vegetarian and I'm not like hey
look at me you know I'm a bus riding
vegetarian
I don't care if you eat meat you could
tackle a cow right in front of me and
start on on it and i' be like I think
that's you're right under the
Constitution go ahead you know and if
the cow started winning I would jump
down there and start fighting the cow
with you you know I'd be like I'm not
going to eat this thing but you're
losing to a cow right
now start hitting this cow you know but
my friends always try to trip me up you
know to see if I'll eat meat they come
up with these wild hypothetical
situations like what if you were trapped
in the mountains in a blizzard and you
fought your way into a cabin and all was
in the freezer was venison would you eat
meat and I'm like yeah I'd eat meat
because I'm a vegetarian not an idiot
you
know I want to live to eat vegetables
another day man
I can't get by the whole one day without
vegetables to keep the string alive and
correct me if I'm wrong but we're
trapped in a blizzard right I would eat
you if it came down to it
I just happen to have a plastini knife
here I was stabbed twice in the cabin
you
know that's knife fighting tip number
two and I don't know the sales are going
to go for the you know uh workout tape
but if we sell enough of them I'll have
a free knif fighting
seminar outside oh
man I love you guys because you surprise
me every step of the way I love that now
I do want to talk about some pertinent
issues you know I think that the whole
problem is oil and it's not that we need
to conserve it we need to use it all up
cuz they're not going to do anything
until it's gone you know
so knowing that I bought a 78 Buick
Electra and I put it up on blocks and
I'm just running it 247
man and I'm doing it on stolen credit
cards so
hey and I want to talk about the
national debt too you know the national
debt is a big thing and every every time
I hear someone talking about the
national debt they say things like I
don't want to see our grandchildren
paying off the national debt and I'm
like I do you know that is the only plan
that makes sense so far man let's put
these kids to
work hey Billy here's a new game called
sewing machine
son sit down here and see how many of
these shoes you can make in 12 hours
all
right fair enough that's
good well you know and like I say I mean
uh I go for a lot of walks and I don't
know what it is about the way that I
look but people who don't even know I'm
a standup comic feel comfortable enough
to come up to me on the street and say
things to me like Beetle Juice Beetle
Juice
beet I'm like that is really rude I
uh I don't go up to people I think are
weird looking and go Lutheran Lutheran
Lutheran I don't know if you've ever
hung out with a pack of Lutheran but you
know all right now I want to tell this
story and this you know I don't like to
brag but I live in a one-bedroom
apartment uh things are going
well again thank you over here man but I
come home one night after a show and I
go into my kitchen which surprisingly
enough has the same
wall it's a crazy coincidence but I hear
this dripping sound behind the wall so I
contact my landlord you know I text him
it's early enough and he says hey check
all the faucets and stuff I check that
stuff there's no leaks he goes okay what
they're going to do is send up a couple
of Maintenance men tomorrow and so they
do they send up these two maintenance
guys Mark and Troy right and they go
over to the wall and they listen and
they go uh yeah it sounds like there's a
leak behind the wall I'm like man I want
to work with you guys you know like I
find the problem you come over and go
yep that's what it is then I felt like I
was in a bad improv
exercise I'm like What's Next fellas
what do you think you know so they go uh
there's it's a three-story building I'm
on the second floor they go we're going
to go up to the third floor so I'm like
all right they go up there they're up
there for like five minutes and then
they come back down and the dripping
sound stopped and they said what you
were hearing was the bathtub
faucet dripping into the Basin on the
third floor and so I played along at
first you know I'm like okay but then I
started thinking about it and like is my
hearing really that good that I could
hear that and shouldn't I be hearing all
kinds of other stuff you know and did
they tell those people that I could hear
their bathtub dripping and they're like
that guy has a weird eye but he hears
like a bat you
know so like I don't know 10 days go by
and my landlord calls and goes hey the
apartment below you there's water
dripping through I go that's weird do
you think it had anything to do you know
with that leing sound I reported almost
two weeks
ago so so now I don't know what happened
to Mark in this joke but Troy is up in
my uh apartment
and the guy below is George and he owns
the other apartment and they're doing
all these tests right talking on the
phone Troy has the bathroom the the tub
on any leaks nope no leaks you know then
he puts on the shower and they go hey
I'm no plumber but I'd be willing to bet
if the tub's not leaking the shower is
going to be good too so I want a 100
bucks from Troy that
day so they do all these tests they
can't figure it out and then um George
comes up and it's George Troy and me in
my bathroom and uh wow you guys are
making up your own jokes
again George looks over at me and says
John do you take a lot of baths I'm like
wow that's a weird question but his
theory was I was taking baths and
filling up the tub so much that it was
overflowing you know into the apartment
below so the reason I bring this up you
guys is when I walked out on stage I'm
sure you all made a judge judement about
me I get it I'm in public all the time I
ride the bus I make judgments too but I
would be willing to bet that not one
person here tonight when I walked up on
this stage said to themselves I'll bet
that guy takes a lot of bath
you like I come home after a hard
day man what a day bath bomb boom I'm
taking a bath I'm filling it to the rim
it was me George how about that all
right I'm going to get going here in
just a minute I still have uh something
I want to talk about you guys been so
much fun going to put this in there you
know a lot of comics sell merch after
the show and dry bar is nice enough to
let me do a merch plug so hang on just
for one second
I I've got my Merchant here I'm
uh I am selling a book
tonight I didn't write it but I am
selling it
so I just have the one so see me in a
hurry and I'm also still in
this thin spaghetti uh I bought 10 of
them and I don't really like it so it's
$1 OBO
uh all right and if you're watching this
online message me because I don't know
if this stuff's going to sell tonight or
not all right that's it for me you guys
thank you all so much enjoy
the for